{
    "target_configs": {
        "player": {
            "name": [
                "player_4_5F69D9",
                "player_15_5F69D9",
                "player_6_5F69D9",
                "player_3_5F69D9"
            ],
            "app_id": [
                4,
                15,
                6,
                3
            ],
            "animation": [
                "crouch",
                "stand",
                "crouch",
                "liedown"
            ],
            "feature_caption": [
                "A woman with fair skin, wearing a white and blue shirt, blue pants, dark boots, a gray bandana, and a utility belt with pouches",
                "A bald man with medium skin, wearing a brown turtleneck, dark pants, and brown shoes.",
                "A female soldier with light skin, wearing a black beanie, tactical vest, black shirt, pants, and boots, with a white scarf and communication gear.",
                "A woman with medium skin, dark hair in a bun, wearing a dark V-neck shirt, light pants, and brown boots"
            ],
            "start_pos": [
                [
                    -59555.947,
                    85713.451,
                    -5803.759,
                    0,
                    65.59494743951066,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    -59807.194,
                    85456.476,
                    -5815.525,
                    0,
                    -78.48483146735346,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    -60340.827,
                    85168.931,
                    -5825.143,
                    0,
                    -179.86989660353652,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    -60412.929,
                    85423.617,
                    -5799.128,
                    0,
                    -14.334964058943626,
                    0
                ]
            ],
            "type": [
                "None",
                "None",
                "None",
                "None",
                "None"
            ]
        }
    },
    "sample_configs": {
        "sample_center": [
            -60259.792,
            85740.378,
            -5744.284
        ],
        "sample_radius": 1234.0048641694148
    },
    "refer_agents_category": [
        "player"
    ],
    "safe_start": [
        [
            -60541.907,
            85965.852,
            -5707.04,
            0,
            -40.50878190583969,
            0
        ],
        [
            -60179.513,
            84379.644,
            -5849.832,
            0,
            74.33511764264023,
            0
        ],
        [
            -58960.85,
            85224.931,
            -5899.731,
            0,
            168.7728436393692,
            0
        ]
    ],
    "Questions": {
        "relative_distance": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_woman_in_floral_shirt, the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants or the_woman_in_black_vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants",
                    "B. the_woman_in_black_vest"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_woman_in_floral_shirt, the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants or the_woman_in_deep_V_top?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants",
                    "B. the_woman_in_deep_V_top"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants, the_woman_in_floral_shirt or the_woman_in_black_vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_floral_shirt",
                    "B. the_woman_in_black_vest"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_woman_in_floral_shirt"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants, the_woman_in_floral_shirt or the_woman_in_deep_V_top?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_floral_shirt",
                    "B. the_woman_in_deep_V_top"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_woman_in_floral_shirt"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_woman_in_black_vest, the_woman_in_deep_V_top or the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_deep_V_top",
                    "B. the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_woman_in_deep_V_top"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_woman_in_black_vest, the_woman_in_deep_V_top or the_woman_in_floral_shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_deep_V_top",
                    "B. the_woman_in_floral_shirt"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_woman_in_deep_V_top"
            },
            "Question 7": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_woman_in_deep_V_top, the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants or the_woman_in_floral_shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants",
                    "B. the_woman_in_floral_shirt"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants"
            },
            "Question 8": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_woman_in_deep_V_top, the_woman_in_black_vest or the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_black_vest",
                    "B. the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_woman_in_black_vest"
            }
        },
        "counting": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "How many distinct human figures are visible in the scene?",
                "answer": "four"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "How many individuals are in a crouched position?",
                "answer": "two"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "How many figures are lying still on the earth?",
                "answer": "one"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "How many individuals are standing and surveying the vast, somber world?",
                "answer": "one"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "How many female individuals are present in the scene?",
                "answer": "three"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "How many people in the scene are characterized as having a bald head?",
                "answer": "one"
            },
            "Question 7": {
                "question": "How many individuals in the scene have a light skin complexion?",
                "answer": "three"
            },
            "Question 8": {
                "question": "Considering all individuals in the scene, how many are explicitly noted as *not* wearing glasses?",
                "answer": "four"
            }
        },
        "state": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "What's the state of the woman in the floral shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. crouch",
                    "B. standing",
                    "C. lying down",
                    "D. walking"
                ],
                "answer": "A. crouch"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "What's the state of the bald man?",
                "options": [
                    "A. sitting",
                    "B. standing",
                    "C. crouch",
                    "D. kneeling"
                ],
                "answer": "B. standing"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "What's the state of the woman in the black vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. running",
                    "B. standing",
                    "C. crouch",
                    "D. walking"
                ],
                "answer": "C. crouch"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "What's the state of the woman in the deep V-top?",
                "options": [
                    "A. standing",
                    "B. sitting",
                    "C. lying down",
                    "D. crouch"
                ],
                "answer": "C. lying down"
            }
        },
        "relative_location": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "Where is the bald man in brown sweater and black pants relative to the woman in floral shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front-right of",
                    "B. To the back-left of",
                    "C. To the front of",
                    "D. Behind"
                ],
                "answer": "B. To the back-left of"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in deep V top relative to the woman in floral shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. In front of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "B. Behind"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in floral shirt relative to the bald man in brown sweater and black pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the back-left of",
                    "B. To the front-right of",
                    "C. Behind",
                    "D. To the left of"
                ],
                "answer": "B. To the front-right of"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in black vest relative to the bald man in brown sweater and black pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front-right of",
                    "B. To the back-left of",
                    "C. To the front of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "B. To the back-left of"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in deep V top relative to the bald man in brown sweater and black pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. In front of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "B. Behind"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in floral shirt relative to the woman in black vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the back-left of",
                    "B. To the front-right of",
                    "C. Behind",
                    "D. To the left of"
                ],
                "answer": "B. To the front-right of"
            },
            "Question 7": {
                "question": "Where is the bald man in brown sweater and black pants relative to the woman in black vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the back-left of",
                    "B. To the front-right of",
                    "C. Behind",
                    "D. To the left of"
                ],
                "answer": "B. To the front-right of"
            },
            "Question 8": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in deep V top relative to the woman in black vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front of",
                    "B. To the back of",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "D. To the right of"
            }
        }
    }
}